gadzoo.com 2014-04-30

# Welcome to Gadzoo.com

Privacy Policy Last Updated: August 2010

**Please read the following privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") carefully before using Gadzoo.com or any site powered by Legacy.com or Gadzoo.com (collectively, this "Site").**

### 1\. What This Privacy Policy Covers

  1. This Privacy Policy covers how Gadzoo.com, Inc. (collectively, "Gadzoo.com", "we", "us", or "our") and all of its associated Web sites, products, and services (collectively, the "Services") treats user or personally identifiable information that the Services collect and receive. If, however, you are accessing this Privacy Policy from a Web site operated in conjunction with one of our affiliates (listed at <http://www.gadzoo.com/GadzooAffiliatesHome.aspx?state=All>), the privacy policy of the Affiliate will govern unless such policy states otherwise. 
  2. Subject to the above, this Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Gadzoo.com does not own, operate or control, or to people that it does not employ or manage. 

### 2\. General

In general, you can visit the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Gadzoo.com does not collect personally identifiable information about individuals, except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals on interactive areas of the Site. "Personally Identifiable Information" is information that can be used to uniquely identify, contact, or locate a single person, such as name, postal address, email address, phone number, and credit card number, among other information, and that is not otherwise publicly available. Any posting made while using the Site and Services can be viewed by the public and therefore is not considered "personal information" or "Personally Identifiable Information" and is not the type of information covered by this Privacy Policy. 

### 3\. Information We Collect

  1. Personally Identifiable Information. 
    * Examples of Personally Identifiable Information we collect include name, postal address, email address, credit card number and related information, and phone number. We also maintain a record of all information that you submit to us, including email and other correspondence. We may collect Personally Identifiable Information when you register to receive alerts or offerings, sponsor or submit information in connection with certain Services, post other content on the Site, purchase products or other services, opt-in to receive special offers and discounts from us and our selected partners or participate in other activities offered or administered by Gadzoo.com. 
    * We may also collect Personally Identifiable Information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners. This information might include information necessary to process payments due to us from you, such as your credit card number. 
    * We do not intentionally collect Personally Identifiable Information about children under the age of 13. Please see the section on "Children’s Privacy" below. 
  2. Other Anonymous Information. 
    * Like most websites, Gadzoo.com also receives and records information on our server logs from your browser automatically and through the use of electronic tools such as cookies. Our server logs automatically receive and record information from your browser (including, for example, your IP address, and the page(s) you visit). The information gathered through these methods is not "personally identifiable;" i.e., it cannot be used to uniquely identify, contact, or locate a single person. 

### 4\. How We Use Your Information

  1. We will use your information only as permitted by law, and subject to the terms of our Privacy Policy; 
  2. Use of Personally Identifiable Information: 
    * We do not sell or share your Personally Identifiable Information with unrelated third parties for their direct marketing purposes. 
    * Personally Identifiable Information and other personal information you specifically provide may be used: 
      * to provide the Services we offer, to process transactions and billing, for identification and authentication purposes, to communicate with you concerning transactions, security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of the Site and Services, to improve Services, to do something you have asked us to do, or to tell you of Services that we think may be of interest to you. 
      * to communicate with you regarding our Site and Services.
      * for the administration of and troubleshooting regarding the Site. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of the Site (our web hosting service, for example), may need to access such information from time to time, but are not permitted to disclose such information to others. 
    * We may disclose Personally Identifiable Information about you under the following circumstances: 
      * In the course of operating our business, it may be necessary or appropriate for us to provide access to your Personally Identifiable Information to others such as our service providers, contractors, select vendors and Affiliates so that we can operate the Site and our business. Where practical, we will seek to obtain confidentiality agreements consistent with this Privacy Policy and that limit others’ use or disclosure of the information you have shared. 
      * We may share your Personally Identifiable Information if we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to: (1) comply with the law or with legal process (such as pursuant to court order, subpoena, or a request by law enforcement officials); (2) protect, enforce, and defend our Terms of Use, rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of this Site; or (4) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public (among other things, this means that if you provide false information or attempt to pose as someone else, information about you may be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions.) 
  3. Use of Anonymous Information: 
    * Certain information that we collect automatically or with electronic tools (such as cookies) is used to anonymously track and measure user traffic to this Site and to enhance your experience on this Site. For example: 
      * IP Addresses/Session Information. We occasionally may obtain IP addresses from users depending upon how you access our Site. IP addresses, browser, and session information may be used for various purposes, including to help administer this Site and diagnose and prevent service or other technology problems related to this Site. This information also may be used to estimate the total number of users visiting the Site from specific geographical areas, to help determine which users have access privileges to certain content or services that we offer, and to monitor and prevent fraud and abuse. IP addresses are not linked to Personally Identifiable Information 
      * Cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data that often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a website’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive. You can configure your browser to accept cookies, reject them, or notify you when a cookie is set. If you reject cookies, you may not be able to use our Services that require you to sign in, or to take full advantage of all our offerings. Cookies may involve the transmission of information either directly to us or to another party we authorize to collect information on our behalf. We use our own cookies to transmit information for a number of purposes, including to: 
      * require you to re-enter your password after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accessing your account contents; 
      * keep track of preferences you specify while you are using the Site;
      * estimate and report our total audience size and traffic; 
      * conduct research to improve the content and services provided on the Site. 
We let other entities that show advertisements on some of our web pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other entities’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies and not this Privacy Policy. Advertisers or other entities do not have access to our cookies. 
    * We may share anonymous information aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed, etc. with our partners, advertisers and others. 

### 5\. Privacy Alert: Your Site Postings Generally Are Accessible to the Public

  1. Your own use of the Site may disclose personal information or Personally Identifiable Information to the public. For example: 
    * This Site makes submissions, and other postings to our Services available for viewing by all our visitors unless the sponsor or host of a Service selects a privacy setting that restricts public access. Please remember that any information disclosed on a non-restricted Service becomes public information and may be collected and used by others without our knowledge. You therefore should exercise caution when disclosing any personal information or Personally Identifiable Information in these forums. 
    * When you post a message to any message board, blog, or other public forum on the Site, your user ID or alias that you are posting under may be visible to other users, and you have the ability to post a message that may include personal information. 
  2. If you post Personally Identifiable Information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Such activities are beyond the control of Gadzoo.com and the coverage of this Privacy Policy. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online. In addition, although we employ technology and software designed to minimize spam sent to users and unsolicited, automatic posts to message boards, blogs, or other public forums on the Site (like the CAPTCHA word verification you see on email and registration forms), we cannot ensure such measures to be 100% reliable or satisfactory. 

### 6\. Children’s Privacy

  1. Gadzoo.com does not intentionally collect from or maintain Personally Identifiable Information of children under the age of 13, nor do we offer any content targeted to such children. 
  2. In the event that Gadzoo.com becomes aware that a user of the Site is under the age of 13, the following additional privacy terms and notices apply: 
    * Prior to collecting any Personally Identifiable Information about a child that Gadzoo.com has become aware is under the age of 13, Gadzoo.com will make reasonable efforts to contact the child’s parent, to inform the parent about the types of information Gadzoo.com will collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances it will be disclosed, and to obtain consent from the child's parent to collection and use of such information. 
    * Although Gadzoo.com will apply these children's privacy terms whenever it becomes aware that a user who submits Personally Identifiable Information is less than 13 years old, no method is foolproof. Gadzoo.com strongly encourages parents and guardians to supervise their children's online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers to help provide a child-friendly online environment. These tools also can prevent children from disclosing online their name, address, and other personal information without parental permission. 
    * Personally Identifiable Information collected from children may include any of the information defined above as Personally Identifiable Information with respect to general users of the Site and may be used by Gadzoo.com for the same purposes. Except as necessary to process a child's requests or orders placed with advertisers or merchants featured on the Site, Gadzoo.com does not rent, sell, barter or give away any lists containing a child's Personally Identifiable Information for use by any outside company. 
    * A child's parent or legal guardian may request Gadzoo.com to provide a description of the Personally Identifiable Information that Gadzoo.com has collected from the child, as well as instruct Gadzoo.com to cease further use, maintenance and collection of Personally Identifiable Information from the child. 
    * If a child voluntarily discloses his or her name, email address or other personally-identifying information on chat areas, bulletin boards or other forums or public posting areas, such disclosures may result in unsolicited messages from other parties. 

### 7\. Ownership

Gadzoo.com and/or the Affiliates are the sole owner(s) of the information collected on this Site.

### 8\. Security Measures

The security and confidentiality of your Personally Identifiable Information is extremely important to us. We have implemented technical, administrative, and physical security measures to protect guest information from unauthorized access and improper use. From time to time, we review our security procedures in order to consider appropriate new technology and methods. Please be aware though that, despite our best efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, and no data transmissions over the web can be guaranteed 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. 

### 9\. Correcting or Updating Information

You may modify and correct Personally Identifiable Information provided directly to Gadzoo.com in connection with the Services, if necessary. Gadzoo.com offers users the following options for updating information: 

  1. Send an email to us at info@Gadzoo.com; or 
  2. Send a letter to us via postal mail to the following address:  
Gadzoo.com 820 Davis Street Suite 210 Evanston, IL 60201 Attention: Operations 

### 10\. Opt-Out Procedures

You may opt out of receiving future mailings or other information from Gadzoo.com. If the mailing does not have an email cancellation form, send an email to info@Gadzoo.com detailing the type of information that you no longer wish to receive. 

### 11\. Third Party Advertising and Ad Delivery

  1. This Site contains links to other sites that may be of interest to our visitors. This Privacy Policy applies only to Gadzoo.com and not to other companies' or organizations' Web sites to which we link. We are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by other sites. 
  2. Gadzoo.com works with third parties, including Adtech US, Inc. (“Adtech”), for the purpose of advertisement delivery on the Site and affiliated Web sites. The non-personally identifiable information collected about a consumer’s visits to this and other Web sites, including, but not limited to, certain information from your Web browser and your IP address, may be used by third parties, including Adtech, in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Third parties, including Adtech, may also set cookies to assist with their advertisement delivery services. For more information about Adtech cookies, and how to opt out, please visit <http://www.adtechus.com/privacy/>. Please keep in mind that if you click on an advertisement on the Site or affiliated Web sites and link to a third party's website, then Gadzoo.com’s Privacy Policy will not apply to any Personally Identifiable Information collected on that third party's website and you must read the privacy policy posted on that site to see how your Personally Identifiable Information will be handled. 

### 12\. Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may periodically edit or update this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy whenever you provide information on this Web site. Your use of the Site after changes of the terms of the Privacy Policy have been posted will mean that you accept the changes. 

### 13\. Additional Information

Questions regarding the Gadzoo.com Privacy Policy should be directed to info@Gadzoo.com or  
Gadzoo.com 820 Davis Street Suite 210 Evanston, IL 60201 Attention: Operations 

YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS  
(As provided by California Civil Code Section 1798.83) 

A California resident who has provided personal information to a business with whom he/she has established a business relationship for personal, family, or household purposes ("California customer") is entitled to request information about whether the business has disclosed personal information to any third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. 

Gadzoo.com does not share information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If, however, you are accessing this Privacy Policy from one of our Affiliate sites, the privacy policy of our Affiliate will apply to the collection of your information unless the Affiliate’s privacy policy specifically states otherwise. You should review the privacy policy of the Affiliate to understand what information may be collected from you and how it may be used. 

California customers may request further information about our compliance with this law by emailing info@Gadzoo.com.
